Ladies and gentlemen
Seekers and survive
Tonight specimen and they're smiling
No, no pitch for no open hate just five questions and a coupon for betrayal
That didn't know that didn't know that didn't know that didn't know
Letting soft with the halo to just checking on you pretty loaded
You said I care. You said I see he brought fake loyalty
Free
You learn my man, you're not real hard and set the trap
We call it concern, and I call it death You leave with screenshots tucked in your chest
You want the teeth, the keys, the codes The private bank, the hidden roads
Not here to heal, not here to build Just here to see where the offer is
Too many questions, not enough so Too much sugar in the casserole
Too much on neutral, too much on good, too much smoke for the nice guy
I
Carousine they whisper here and drift right there drop in concern
Person a gets his bite stuff
Person b gets a soft uh, no
What person see gets a hate all drama?
First I'm the department, I'm manufactured karma
Now the room fills with the wires all crossed
Trust gets text and the vibe gets lost
That's not magically the sleight of hand
A sewer wizard with a needy brand
Can't build a stage, can't hold a room
So they brand freeze phase
Another folks doom
Always nearby when the mess appears
Always so shocked with crocodile tears
Always protecting, always concerned
Funny how bridges behind the-
Worryed while they gossiped to all
But they troll, but they troll
And the G leave at the banquet
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Blitter on top, but the core is small
Fake-ass friend near the temple call
Package truth and sell the stain Danger two, they split the crew
Make folks doubt what they already knew Danger three, they bait reaction, them point and scream
Look bad attraction No sweetheart, you build the maze
Now you're acting scared of the fire you raise Danger four, they drain your heart
Deble your focus part by part Not always trying to win the war
Sometimes they just wanna wreck the floor What's the cure?
Slow that trust What's the tip?
Patterns first What's the rule?
Lock that gate What if they pound?
Too damn late Guard your grief
Don't overshare Watch boundaries
won't mind your hurt for a social trick, won't play translate a pre-sense thought, won't hug you close while sharpening lies
a real friend comes a fake one, stirs a real friend, asks a fake one, there's a real friend keeps the chamber sealed
A fake one wants your wounds revealed
So if they rush like this and he's cloned
With hungry eyes and a borrowed tone
Don't handle them candles, keys or gold
Some demons freeze when the door gets closed
But detrol, but detrol
Cheap little ghoul in a satin robe
Moonwalks slip through the loophole
Till the lies come up
And we name it all
But detrol, but...
But familiar with the hungry soul, you wanted the temple, the map, the scroll
Now dance back out to the banishment hole
But didn't deny, but didn't deny, no more entry, not at all
But didn't deny, but didn't deny, truth is hotter than a mirror ball
Truth to yard, out you roll, exit left, little buddy trolls
My law you want, we know the road case closed on a buddy troll
out the show it's not really boycotting the show to still be here I mean it's
usually just play go if you don't want to you don't want to be here or if you
just were looking for I don't know people looking for I'm gonna link up kind of
frustrating you know watching like you know liars succeed and
the truth being censored, but where are these people right now? Where are they all? Where is
their streams up right now? Trying to have lives and conversations and talks? No, they're not up,
they're not. They just want you to like, you know, be on their schedule, be on their time.
They're not even streaming every day. I haven't seen hardly anybody streaming the past few days,
and so, you know, I don't know. Trying to give people a place to hang out and stuff, but I don't
You know, leaving YouTube and shit, but...
It is a little bit, you know, YouTube's already fucking me over, they say,
Oh, well, you know, we can't monetize you because, you know, of your content.
When I wasn't even monetizing the content, I was, I didn't even have
ads on or anything. Oh, you're telling Tony? Well, go tell your, go tell your little bitch, bitch boy.
Go ahead.
Bye. Stay out of my chat.
Go fuck yourself
Anyway
You see yeah, that means it's like that guy's gonna get oh my god any kind of credibility. No, I'll leave long before that happens
Yeah, I really wish he would do to other people what he does to me
So people could like feel for themselves what it's like to get like knots on the door all day
People look at perspons and weed whackers and free bicycles
Nobody even cared about that really, you know
But I guess people don't know something called empathy like how would you feel that was and so everyone just celebrates him
I guess and so he's getting what he wants and you know, sometimes the bad guys win
I'm gonna at least you know fight back as long as I can
With just the truth I
Don't know I guess nobody wants to truth the truth is like the truth is ugly sometimes and
The lies are attractive and dressed, you know, and so
You try to get people to hang out immediately kick someone from the chat. Yeah, somebody that's threatening you Tony. Yeah, okay, right?
Trying not not trying to give you places to hang out trying to give like cool people
Yeah, I'll kick you out of the shed too. I don't care. Bye
leave
Not having people just harass me in shadow day. It's not what that's not what it's about
You can go talk shit about me on Sam and's panel or
You know be as beat his panel or anywhere else. They like to harass me
defame me and you know these people that are like
Not even on camera, right? Okay. She's your she's your side. It's fine. Do you want to choose sides, you know?
Oh, it's Amanda I'm here to give like people that want to hang out like in a positive way not harass me
IRL which is happening right now, right? I'm not gonna give you guys a place to hang out. No
I'm gonna give you a quick ban
And then everyone else is like afraid because I know you know because sometimes like people that are like followers are afraid to talk and
It's like you're like, well, what's everyone gonna think? What's everyone gonna say when they're in band from these chats and everything?
Oh, I need to do nothing. I need to do nothing. I'm just sort. I need to do nothing for you. Bye
All I need to do is kick you out of the chat
And I will and it's like, you know, it's good just reveal yourself and I'll just kick you out of the chat
But if people that actually want to talk and want to have fun, you know, you can say something
and you can pretty much say anything.
You can say anything here except like fucking stuff about that person who's actually criminally
harassing me.
And you're just an accomplice if you're participating in that.
So you're a criminal accomplice.
Okay?
I'll make sure everyone knows it too.
So you can see the people on the screen you can see what their names are just to watch out for those people
They're all probably all the same person
Yeah
But yeah, if no one's to support me anymore
Well, they weren't really good friends in the first place
you know
They're just so willing to like, you know, especially if they like, you know
If you dig into things a little bit like any beyond like the surface level you'll see what's really going on
But no one wants to see the truth
Again, ugly truth is, you know, or a beautiful lie is more attractive than an ugly truth.
Sometimes the truth is ugly.
Sometimes you'll see, like, how misled you've been and, like, what's really going on.
But, sorry, I don't have beautiful truths for you here.
I have, like, you know, I just have the truth.
The truth is not really pretty right now, like, what's been going on.
these gangs forming, these slander, these like smear campaigns, these ostracism campaigns.
I never tell you where to go or not to go.
You can go to anywhere you want. I don't care.
I'm not allowed in most of these places anymore.
My voice has been silenced.
You know, I can't go and beat his panel. I can't go and beat his chat.
I can't go in Christine's chat. I can't go. I'm just not welcome in many places. And so
Barely barely have my own show to go on right now. So
But not one positive thing today
Concrete Larry. Yeah, I see it. I mean you guys can just see the concrete Larry, right? So I'm just gonna keep banning them
You know, I don't know why these people are in my chat and like nobody else's but yeah
Just to scram if you're like, I don't care about the zero people here. What's up, Brandon?
Just fighting the good fight, you know, again, I'll stand up for truth
Like no matter what the truth is, you know and you know just being harassed by this guy Tony
With all these all that you can see on the screen what they've been saying in the chat right now and there's three people here now
Well, good reading this like it's all it's all basically
We know who it is, but the chat will build up again. Like, you know, as soon as I can people figure out the truth
I'm sure then I'll be the most popular person, right?
They are obsessed, right? They're obsessed and they're obsessed with silencing people. Don't go to this person's chat
Oh, yeah, I don't have to keep anybody's name out of my mouth
Okay, I'm gonna especially keep his because his my his name is in my mouth or my name. Yeah, my name is in his mouth, right?
Constantly. Constantly. He's obsessed. I'm obsessed for over a year. He's been sending people to my house
Okay, and I'm obsessed and he's doxing me and chats and I'm obsessed. Okay. Go ahead. I
Mean, no, I mean, I mean not you Brandon, but the person said Sarah somewhere
Sorry to get something stuff
Yeah, I mean it's like YouTube has sort of the demonetizing everybody if they use like thumbnails
Generated by AI if they do anything with and even though YouTube has like all these AI tools that they are encouraged people to use
They didn't warn anybody they just started demonetizing them kept their monthly money. They
What else did they do if they oh then they started putting ads on my content, which I never had before
I always had the option not to put any ads, but I guess they wanted to put ads on the on my content
the whole time so why are they saying that it's not like worthy or whatever
and then they're putting ads on it now I didn't have ads on it before all I had
was a membership going on and they shut down the membership and it's like
um pretty frustrating right and then you're listening to anybody that wants
to flag the channel um you know and so I'm just
Without these like hate watchers over trying to like, you know
Tell on me tattletail and stuff over every little thing for not even stuff
I'm doing it thick people in the panel. It's dangerous running panels. I know it's fucking
Not my link up
Yeah, I did pin the link, okay
but
Yeah, before I get like too depressed about it. I'm probably just gonna
Take a break from YouTube for a while. It's like a little bit
Toxic at this point. It's like, you know, it's I don't want to be under stress. I like to be happy in a good mood
I'll find all the people putting me down and lying about me and attacking me.
It's like maybe I'll go build up my rumble, I'll go build up my kick, I'll go build up
my twitch, I'll go build up my other channels where it's like, or even my TikTok, where
I get a lot of love, instead of just like, yeah, I just have to keep going, but you know,
I've had my ups and downs, it's down right now, but still, I don't have any regrets.
Beating into it. I'm a fighter. I'll fight back against it
I do want people even if it means like, you know the end of my channels
I really need to let people know what's going on
and
Letting these people know
What's really going on who's behind it, but anyway, I'll tell the truth
Even if I have like these 10 minute streams where there's no one no one with anything positive to say but anyway
I guess no one wanted to hang out.
So have a good day, guys, and I'll see you when I see you.
Bye.